giantnerd.com 2019-07-12

# Privacy Policy | Giantnerd

**Giantnerd.com Privacy Policy**

By visiting Giantnerd.com you agree to accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

**Changes to this Privacy Notice, Conditions of Use and Notices:**

This Privacy Notice and our Terms of Use will change over time and the use of information which we gather now is subject to these Notices and Terms as modified. Please check this page periodically as you continue to use our site to see if any changes have been made. This privacy notice was most recently changed on April 1st, 2014. If you visit our web site your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Terms of Use, including the application of the laws of the State of Colorado.

**Personal Information Collected By Giantnerd:**

Giantnerd uses information that we collect from our visitors to personalize and improve your visit at Giantnerd.com. We gather the following types of information:

Information you give us: Giantnerd collects any information which you enter on our Web site. This information is normally provided when you search, buy, participate in an on-line survey, or when you communicate with any of our departments such as customer service, sales or technical support through our Web site, telephone, mail or fax. You also provide information when you establish an account with us. Examples of the type of information you may supply us with include your name, address, telephone number, credit card information and e-mail addresses.

Automatic Information collected by us: Whenever you visit our Web site we collect and store information such as "cookies" which remember information about a visitor from one page to the next and from one visit to the next. We collect and analyze the IP address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; password; computer and connection information such as your browser type and version; operating system and platform; purchase history; confirmation when you open e-mail that we send you; the URLs which lead you to and around our Web site including the date and time; the pages and or products you viewed or searched for and the phone number used to call our voice telephone numbers. Your browser allows you to reject cookies and software is available from third parties which will allow you to visit our Web site without providing this information. You are welcomed at our Web site if you use this software but we will not be able to offer you our personalized services.

Orders: If you place an order we use a secure order form which requires you to provide contact, billing, and financial information. This information is transmitted to your credit card company to authorize your purchase.

**Sharing of Information with third-parties:**

Affiliated Businesses: We may share any information that you supply to us with any affiliated business that is substantially controlled by Giantnerd. Any information that is shared this way will be subject to this Privacy Notice.

Independent Contractors: We may employ other companies or individuals to provide certain services to us such as sending e-mail, analyzing customer lists and data, providing marketing assistance, or consulting services. These third parties will have access to the information needed to perform their functions but cannot use that information for any other purpose.

Credit card companies and shippers: When you buy something from us we send your credit card information, name, billing address and the amount of your purchase to your credit card company to verify and authorize the purchase. Your name, telephone number and shipping information must be provided to third party shippers such as UPS, Federal Express and the United States Postal Service to deliver your purchase.

Link to Third Party Site: Our Web site contains links to third party sites, such as our vendors. Giantnerd is not responsible or liable for the privacy practices or content found on these sites. We suggest that you check the Privacy Notice of each site you visit.

**Law Enforcement and Protection of Users:**

We will release personally identifiable information to third parties and organizations when we believe it is appropriate for us to do so to comply with the law. We will also do so to cooperate with law enforcement investigations, comply with court orders or subpoenas, protect the legal rights of us and our users, or when we believe it is needed for fraud protection.

**Security:**

Our Web site protects the security of personal information you transmit to us by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. We do not reveal your credit card number when we confirm your order. In order to protect against unauthorized access to your account you should sign off when you finish visiting our site.

**Risk of Loss:**

All items purchased from Giantnerd are made pursuant to a shipping contract. This means that the risk of loss and title for such items pass to you upon our delivery to the carrier.
